moreoleinlife.com 2012-12-15

# Privacy Policy - JOSÉ OLÉ® brand

Windsor Foods cares about your privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines the type of Personal Information that is collected by Windsor Foods from consumers and how we use and protect it. This Policy also tells you what to do if you do not want your Personal Information used for marketing purposes and how you can change information that you have already provided to us. This Policy applies to this website and to Windsor Foods’ collection of data through printed promotional materials, such as sweepstakes entry forms, coupons or other mail-in offers, and telephone calls to Windsor Foods’ consumer services department. It does not apply to banners, sweepstakes or promotions sponsored by third parties in which Windsor Foods may participate.

  * Consent to This Privacy Policy
  * Collection of Personal Information
  * How We Use Your Information
  * Cookies: Pixel Tags
  * Retention
  * Security Information
  * Changes in Policy
  * Who to Contact

All references to “Windsor Foods,” “our,” “us” or “we” within this Privacy Policy and opt-in/opt-out notices shall collectively refer to Windsor Quality Food Company, Ltd. and each of their respective parent companies, subsidiaries, affiliates, agents, licensees, transferees, successors and assigns.

**Consent to This Privacy Policy**  
By visiting our website, you signify your acceptance to the terms of this Privacy Policy with respect to information other than Personal Information.

By providing Windsor Foods with Personal Information, you signify that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy Policy with respect to your Personal Information.

If you do not agree with any terms in this Policy, please do not visit this website and/or provide any Personal Information.

If you choose not to provide Personal Information, you may not be able to do certain things, like access particular areas of our website, enter sweepstakes or contests, or send us e-mail.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
As used in this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means personally identifiable information about you that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, street address, telephone number, credit card information, screen name and e-mail address.

When you provide us with Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, which includes your right to limit our use of your Personal Information (see Who to Contact).

We may also collect Personal Information from you about a third party — for instance, you may ask us to forward information from our site to a friend or associate of yours, in which case we will need that person's name and e-mail address. Please note that we use such information only for the specified purpose (e.g., to mail the information) and we will not contact the third party again, unless and until the third party contacts us.

**How We Use Your Information**  
When you supply us with Personal Information, we will use it for the express purpose for which it was collected (e.g., to enter you in a sweepstakes). It may also be used to contact you regarding other products and services that may be of interest to you, including those that we may offer jointly with other companies. At any time, however, you may choose to opt out of such contact (see Who to Contact).

We sometimes may retain third parties to analyze data that we collect, including Personal Information, to help us improve our products and our website. In addition, if you order a product or a service from us, we may provide Personal Information to suppliers and other third parties to enable delivery of such product or service. These third parties, including suppliers, are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information in any way other than that specified. Windsor Foods does not sell Personal Information.

We may supplement the information that you provide to us with other information that we receive from third parties. We do this for marketing purposes, in order to provide the most appropriate products and services to meet your needs.

We may also transfer, sell or assign your Personal Information to any entity to which we divest all or a portion of our business (for example, in connection with our sale of a brand), to the extent that you provided such information to the specific portion of our business (or brand) that is being divested, or otherwise in connection with a merger, consolidation, change in control, reorganization or liquidation of all or a portion of our business.

Finally, please note that we will release your Personal Information if required to do so by law, or by search warrant, subpoena or court order.

**Cookies: Pixel Tags**  
You may have heard of “cookies,” which are files or pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Windsor Foods may use cookies to collect information during your visit to our website to help us understand how you use our site, which areas of the site are used the most, and to document the products or services that you buy through our website. We collect this information to better tailor our site and our products to your interests and needs. We also use cookies to customize your experience of our site and to help speed up your future activities at the site. For example, using cookies, the site can recognize that you already have provided Personal Information to us and it can refrain from requesting the same information again.

Most browsers can be set to accept cookies, to refuse them, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Refusal of cookies at this site may result in an inability to visit certain areas of the site or to receive personalized information when you visit the site.

To help us improve the effectiveness of our presence online, and to determine how we may better promote our site, we may collect information from your browser about how you found our site or what you clicked on to get to our site.

Site measurement statistics also may be used to personalize your website experience, as well as to evaluate — anonymously and in the aggregate — statistics about usage of the website. Information about your computer, such as your IP address (a number assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Internet), the type of Internet browser you are using, and the type of computer operating system you are using may also be collected and linked to your Personal Information. This is to ensure that our website presents you with the best possible web experience and that it communicates information effectively.

Finally, some of the pages that you visit may use pixel tags (also called clear gifs) to collect information about your navigation on our website. This information is used to evaluate and to enhance how the website functions. Pixel tags are not used to collect any Personal Information apart from what you voluntarily provide us.

**Retention**  
Windsor Foods will retain your Personal Information for only so long as is necessary to fulfill the purposes to which you have consented or as required by law. For example, we may be subject to legal requirements with respect to the retention of documents such as sweepstakes entry forms.

**Security of Information** Windsor Foods takes reasonable precautions to guard against unauthorized access to your Personal Information and to safely store your Personal Information. All personally identifiable information is subject to restricted access to prevent unauthorized access, modification or misuse. The Internet, however, is not a secure medium. Therefore, the privacy of your communications and Personal Information can never be guaranteed.

**Links to Other Websites**  
We cannot assume any responsibility for the privacy and data collection practices of third-party websites to which this website is linked. Such third-party websites are independent of this website and not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should review the privacy policies of all websites to which this website may be linked.

**Changes in Policy**  
Windsor Foods reserves the right to change or remove this Privacy Policy at our discretion. We will post any new policy here and we encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 8, 2008.

**Who to Contact**  
Please write to us at **** Jose Ole®, 612 S. Harbor Blvd. Anaheim, CA 92805 or call us at 1-877-653-2181 if you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or about your Personal Information and how it is being used, collected or disclosed, or to report any violations of the Privacy Policy. We will respond to you within three business days in most cases. 

For other requests, please choose among the following options:

If you **don't want to be contacted** in the future or would like us to **correct or update your Personal Information** in our records, please select one of the following options and click on the appropriate button below.

You gave us your contact information through our sweepstakes:

You gave us your contact information through our regular contact page:

Windsor Foods will take reasonable steps to comply with the foregoing requests.

Again, Windsor Foods is committed to protecting your privacy. Please do not hesitate to contact us if you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy.
